Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
Joseph Lindon Smith papers
- Printed Material, 1723-1963, Series 9:; (Box 8, OV 11; 0.8 linear feet)
  - Clippings, 1939 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Clippings, 1940-1941 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Clippings, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Clippings, 1945-1948 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Clippings, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Clippings, 1950-1951 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Clippings, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Clippings, 1953-1955 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Clippings, 1956, (3 folders) (Box 8, Folder 30-32)
  - Clippings, 1957-1963 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - By-Laws and Newsletters for the American Research Center in Egypt, Inc., 1950-1954, (2 folders) (Box 8, Folder 34-35)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs for the Smith Family, 1891-1953, undated, (2 folders) (Box 8, Folder 36-37)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs for Others, 1949-1952, undated (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Press Releases, 1920-1954 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Programs, 1900-1963, undated (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Booklet Country Life in Ancient Egypt, undated (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Booklet Sculptures Indiennes de la Collection Paul Mallon by Victor Goloubew, undated (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Booklet Spiritual Songs for Children by J. Wright, 1784 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Booklet A Poem on the Lord's Day: Together with Acrostics on General Washington and President Adams, 1800 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Booklet A Short Account of the Last Sickness and Death of Maria Mott, 1817 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Booklet The American Tract Magazine, 1824 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Booklet Synopsis of Phrenology, 1849 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Booklet Un Mese Nella Necropoli di Tebe by A. Malvezzi, 1905 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Booklet The Introductory Gresham Lecture by F. M. Sandwith, 1907 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Booklet L'Isola del Paradiso: Un Viaggio a Ceylon, 1908 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Booklet Jarash, 1926 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Booklet Seminole Indians, 1931 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Booklet Treaty of Alliance, 1936 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Booklet Traffic in Opium and Other Dangerous Drugs, 1938 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Booklet The Morley Collection of Spanish Colonial Ecclesiastical Art, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Booklet The Thursday Evening Club of Boston by Reginald Fitz, 1946 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Booklet Joseph Lindon Smith - The Man and the Artist by Dr. M. Mahdi Allam, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Booklet The Wisdom of Father Andrew by Kathleen E. Burne, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Booklet Angela Behind the Steel Drape by Angela Brown, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Book Ed Dakhleh Oasis by H. E. Winlock, 1936 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Book The Fellaheen by Father Henry Ayrout, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Brochures for Book Tombs, Temples, and Ancient Art by Joseph Lindon Smith, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Miscellaneous Brochures, 1929-1959 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Picture Postcards, undated (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Reproductions of Art Work, undated (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Miscellaneous Printed Material, 1723-1945, (2 folders;Oversized Material Housed in OV 11) (Box 8, Folder 66-67)
  - Oversized Certificate from Imperial Reception at Carnival Palace in New Orleans, 1891, (from Box 8, Folder 66) (Box OV 11)
  - Oversized Printed Salute to Tommy Atkins from George Stewart, 1945 (Box OV 11)
- Photographs, 1884-1956, Series 10:; (Box 8-10; 0.5 linear feet)
  Photographs are of Smith, his family, friends, exhibition installations, scenes from World War I, travel scenes, and art work by Smith.
  - Joseph Lindon Smith, 1910-1947, (2 folders) (Box 8, Folder 68-69)
  - Family Members, 1944-1951, undated, (2 folders) (Box 8, Folder 70-71)
  - Friends, 1884-1955, (5 folders) (Box 8, Folder 72-76)
  - Scenes from World War I, 1918-1919 (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Unidentified Exhibition Installation, undated (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - Exhibition Installation at Atlanta Base, undated (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - Exhibition Installation for Harvard Tercentenary, 1936 (Box 8, Folder 80)
  - Exhibition Installation Honoring George Reisner, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Exhibition Installation in Book Store, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 82)
  - Travel to Cambodia, undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Travel to Egypt, undated, (3 folders) (Box 9, Folder 2-4)
  - Travel to India, undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Travel to Italy (Rome), undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Travel to Japan, 1901-1910, undated, (Oversized Material Housed in Box 10) (Box 9, Folder 7-8)
  - Travel to Jordan (Petra), 1930 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Travel to Mexico, undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Travel to Persia (Persepolis), 1934, (3 folders) (Box 9, Folder 11-13)
  - Travel to the United States (Southwest), 1926 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous Buildings, undated, (Oversized Material Housed in Box 10) (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Art Work by Joseph Lindon Smith from Cambodia, undated (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Art Work by Joseph Lindon Smith from Egypt, undated, (5 folders) (Box 9, Folder 17-21)
  - Art Work by Joseph Lindon Smith from Italy (Rome), undated (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Art Work by Joseph Lindon Smith from Japan, undated, (2 folders) (Box 9, Folder 23-24)
  - Art Work by Joseph Lindon Smith from Java, undated (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Art Work by Joseph Lindon Smith from Jordan (Petra), undated (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Art Work by Joseph Lindon Smith from Mexico, undated, (2 folders) (Box 9, Folder 27-28)
  - Art Work by Joseph Lindon Smith from Persia (Persepolis), undated (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Miscellaneous Art Work by Joseph Lindon Smith, undated (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Miscellaneous Art Work by Others, undated (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Oversized Photographs of Art Work from Japan, undated, from Box 9, Folder 8 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Oversized Photograph of a Minaret in an Unidentified Country, undated, from Box 9, Folder 15 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Audio Recordings, 1956, Series 11:; (Box 9, 10; 2 folders)
  Audio recordings consist of radio interviews with Barry Faulkner and Corinna Lindon Smith, a radio program about Joseph Lindon Smith, and a fragment of an additional interview with Corinna Smith. Original recordings are on four sound discs, all of which were created at WKNE radio in Keene, NH.
  All of the sound recordings in this series have been digitized for research access. Previous copies made on cassette are also available.
  - Interview with Barry Faulkner conducted by Ruth Redington about Joseph Lindon Smith, 1956, (1 original sound disc, 1 duplicate sound cassette, oversized material housed in Box 10) (Box 9, Folder 32, Item 1)
    Side 2 of this recording contains a 9-minute fragment of an interview with Corinna Smith conducted by Ted Sawyer.
  - Interview with Corinna Smith conducted by Howard E. Wheelock about Joseph Lindon Smith, 1956, (1 original sound disc, 1 duplicate sound cassette, oversized material housed in Box 10) (Box 9, Folder 32, Item 2)
  - "Tombs, Temples, and Ancient Art: Joseph Lindon Smith," 1956, (2 original sound discs, 2 duplicate sound cassettes, oversized material housed in Box 10) (Box 9, Folder 32, Item 3)
  - Oversized Sound Recordings, 1956, (from Box 9, folder 32) (Box 10, Folder 7)